<?xml version="1.0"?>
<root>
  <quotes>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>siliconvalley</tvserie>
      <content>Well, you just brought piss to a shit fight, you little cunt!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>siliconvalley</tvserie>
      <content>Gavin Belson started out with lofty goals too, but he just kept excusing immoral behavior just like this, until one day all that was left was a sad man with funny shoes... Disgraced, friendless, and engorged with the blood of a youthful charlatan.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>simpsons</tvserie>
      <content>What&#x2019;s the point of going out? We&#x2019;re just gonna wind up back home anyway.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>Sure I peed on her. And if I had to, I&#x2019;d pee on any one of you!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>drwho</tvserie>
      <content>Never ignore coincidence. Unless, of course, you&#x2019;re busy. In which case, always ignore coincidence.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>got</tvserie>
      <content>Laughter is poison to fear.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>How you doin&#x2019;?</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>got</tvserie>
      <content>Fear cuts deeper than swords.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>got</tvserie>
      <content>Hodor? Hodor.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>got</tvserie>
      <content>... a mind needs books as a sword needs a whetstone, if it is to keep its edge.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>simpsons</tvserie>
      <content>Sorry, Mom, the mob has spoken.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>twinpeaks</tvserie>
      <content>J'ai une &#xE2;me solitaire.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>twinpeaks</tvserie>
      <content>Audrey, there are many cures for a broken heart. But nothing quite like a trout's leap in the moonlight.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>got</tvserie>
      <content>Things are not always as they seemed, much that may seem evil can be good.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>twinpeaks</tvserie>
      <content>COOPER, YOU REMIND ME TODAY OF A SMALL MEXICAN CHIHUAHUA.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>siliconvalley</tvserie>
      <content>I extended my compression algorithm to support... get this... 12-bit color. Okay, so our users will be able to experience a 10 percent increase in image quality with absolutely no increase in server load whatsoever. Just-Just-Just... Just watch this. Before. After. Before. After.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>siliconvalley</tvserie>
      <content>It's weird. They always travel in groups of five. These programmers, there's always a tall, skinny white guy; short, skinny Asian guy; fat guy with a ponytail; some guy with crazy facial hair; and then an East Indian guy. It's like they trade guys until they all have the right group.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>siliconvalley</tvserie>
      <content>And that, gentlemen, is scrum. Welcome to the next eight weeks of our lives.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>Dear God! This parachute is a knapsack!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>simpsons</tvserie>
      <content>Life is just one crushing defeat after another until you just wish Flanders was dead.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>twinpeaks</tvserie>
      <content>MAY A SMILE BE YOUR UMBRELLA. WE'VE ALL HAD OUR SOCKS TOSSED AROUND.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>drwho</tvserie>
      <content>The assembled hordes of Genghis Khan couldn't get through that door, and, believe me, they've tried.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>simpsons</tvserie>
      <content>Go out on a Tuesday? Who am I, Charlie Sheen?</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>got</tvserie>
      <content>A lion doesn't concern itself with the opinion of sheep.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>simpsons</tvserie>
      <content>Oh, loneliness and cheeseburgers are a dangerous mix.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>twinpeaks</tvserie>
      <content>You may think I've gone insane... but I promise. I will kill again.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>siliconvalley</tvserie>
      <content>Hitler actually played the bassoon. So technically Hitler was the Hitler of music.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>Joey doesn&#x2019;t share food!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>If you want to receive emails about my upcoming shows please give me money so I can buy a computer.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>simpsons</tvserie>
      <content>You tried your best and you failed miserably. The lesson is: Never try.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>got</tvserie>
      <content>Give me honorable enemies rather than ambitious ones, and I'll sleep more easily by night.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>got</tvserie>
      <content>Once you&#x2019;ve accepted your flaws, no one can use them against you.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>got</tvserie>
      <content>Power is a curious thing. Who lives, Who dies. Power resides where men believe it resides. It is a trick, A shadow on the wall.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>Your teeth? Yeah, I saw them from outside.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>simpsons</tvserie>
      <content>That's it! You people have stood in my way long enough. I'm going to clown college!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>simpsons</tvserie>
      <content>Kill my boss? Do I dare live out the American dream?</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>twinpeaks</tvserie>
      <content>YOU ARE WITNESSING A FRONT THREE-QUARTER VIEW OF TWO ADULTS SHARING A TENDER MOMENT</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>siliconvalley</tvserie>
      <content>Let me ask you. How fast do you think you could jerk off every guy in this room? Because I know how long it would take me. And I can prove it</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>drwho</tvserie>
      <content>You want weapons? We're in a library! Books! The best weapons in the world!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>siliconvalley</tvserie>
      <content>Gentlemen, I just paid the palapa contractor. The palapa piper, so to speak. The dream is a reality. We'll no longer be exposed... to the elements.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>twinpeaks</tvserie>
      <content>Pie. Whoever invented the pie? Here was a great person.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>I can handle this. Handle is my middle name. Actually, handle is the middle of my first name.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>twinpeaks</tvserie>
      <content>I don't wanna talk. I wanna shoot.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>got</tvserie>
      <content>Nothing burns like the cold.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>If you don&#x2019;t help me cook I&#x2019;m going to take a bunch of those hot dogs and make a new appetiser called pigs in Ross.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>simpsons</tvserie>
      <content>Trust me, Bart, it's better to walk in on both your parents than on just one of them.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>got</tvserie>
      <content>Some old wounds never truly heal, and bleed again at the slightest word.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>siliconvalley</tvserie>
      <content>I don't want to live in a world where someone else is making the world a better place better than we are.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>Until I was 25 I thought the only response to &#x2018;I love you&#x2019; was &#x2018;Oh crap!'</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>siliconvalley</tvserie>
      <content>Of course they know that you're not pitching Shazam. That already exists. This would be a Shazam... for food.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>siliconvalley</tvserie>
      <content>Compromise is the shared hypotenuse of the conjoined triangles of success.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>drwho</tvserie>
      <content>Lots of planets have a north!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>You could not be any more wrong. You could try, but you would not be successful.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>Oh, are you setting Ross up with someone? Does she have a wedding dress?</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>siliconvalley</tvserie>
      <content>You listen to me, you muscle-bound handsome Adonis: tech is reserved for people like me, okay? The freaks, the weirdos, the misfits, the geeks, the dweebs, the dorks! Not you!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>drwho</tvserie>
      <content>Aw, I wanted to be ginger! I've never been ginger!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>simpsons</tvserie>
      <content>I'm not normally a praying man, but if you're up there, please save me, Superman!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>siliconvalley</tvserie>
      <content>I was gonna sleep last night, but, uh... I thought I had this solve for this computational trust issue I've been working on, but it turns out, I didn't have a solve. But it was too late. I had already drank the whole pot of coffee.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>drwho</tvserie>
      <content>The universe is big. It&#x2019;s vast and complicated and ridiculous. And sometimes, very rarely, impossible things just happen and we call them miracles.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>got</tvserie>
      <content>There are no heroes...in life, the monsters win.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>drwho</tvserie>
      <content>Bananas are good.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>siliconvalley</tvserie>
      <content>Line &#x2019;em up, nuts to butts</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>twinpeaks</tvserie>
      <content>There was a fish in the percolator!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>I&#x2019;m not someone who goes after a guy five minutes after he&#x2019;s divorced.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>Oh look, ugly naked guy is decorating his Christmas tree! Wow, you should see the size of his Christmas balls!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>got</tvserie>
      <content>Knowledge could be more valuable than gold, more deadly than a dagger.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>simpsons</tvserie>
      <content>It takes two to lie: one to lie and one to listen.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>siliconvalley</tvserie>
      <content>I simply imagine that my skeleton is me and my content is my house. That way I'm always home.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>drwho</tvserie>
      <content>A straight line may be the shortest distance between two points, but it is by no means the most interesting.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>twinpeaks</tvserie>
      <content>I have no idea where this will lead us. But I have a definite feeling it will be a place both wonderful and strange.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>twinpeaks</tvserie>
      <content>You know, this is &#x2014; excuse me &#x2014; a damn fine cup of coffee!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>drwho</tvserie>
      <content>Your wish is my command. But be careful what you wish for.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>Oh, my God! If you say that one more time, I&#x2019;m going to break up with you!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>drwho</tvserie>
      <content>Bunk beds are cool, a bed with a ladder, you can't beat that!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>Could I BE wearing any more clothes?</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>It was summer&#x2026; and it was hot. Rachel was there&#x2026; A lonely grey couch&#x2026;&#x201D;OH LOOK!&#x201D; cried Ned, and then the kingdom was his forever. The End.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>drwho</tvserie>
      <content>I saw the Fall of Troy! World War Five! I was pushing boxes at the Boston Tea Party! Now I'm gonna die in a dungeon... in Cardiff!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>twinpeaks</tvserie>
      <content>The owls are not what they seem.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>twinpeaks</tvserie>
      <content>How's Annie? How's Annie? How's Annie?</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>twinpeaks</tvserie>
      <content>Wow, Bob, wow.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>got</tvserie>
      <content>When the snows fall and the white winds blow, the lone wolf dies but the pack survives.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>simpsons</tvserie>
      <content>Son, if you really want something in this life, you have to work for it. Now quiet! They're about to announce the lottery numbers.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>I&#x2019;m glad we&#x2019;re having a rehearsal dinner. I rarely practice my meals before I eat.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>simpsons</tvserie>
      <content>D'oh!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>twinpeaks</tvserie>
      <content>There's nothing quite like urinating in the open air.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>twinpeaks</tvserie>
      <content>Where we're from, the birds sing a pretty song, and there's always music in the air.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>No. Interestingly enough, her leaf blower picked up.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>drwho</tvserie>
      <content>900 years of time and space, and I&#x2019;ve never been slapped by someone&#x2019;s mother.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>Ross, just for my own peace of mind, you&#x2019;re not married to any more of us are you?</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>got</tvserie>
      <content>Every flight begins with a fall.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>drwho</tvserie>
      <content>I wear a fez now. Fezzes are cool.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>twinpeaks</tvserie>
      <content>Will this sadness that makes me cry my heart out &#x2014; will it ever end? The answer, of course, is yes. One day the sadness will end.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>twinpeaks</tvserie>
      <content>Every day, once a day, give yourself a present.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>got</tvserie>
      <content>And I have a tender spot in my heart for cripples and bastards and broken things.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>All right, look if you absolutely have to tell her the truth, at least wait until the timing&#x2019;s right. And that&#x2019;s what deathbeds are for.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>It&#x2019;s a moo point. It&#x2019;s like a cow&#x2019;s opinion; it doesn&#x2019;t matter. It&#x2019;s moo.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>twinpeaks</tvserie>
      <content>Black as midnight on a moonless night.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>drwho</tvserie>
      <content>Come on, Rory! It isn't rocket science, it's just quantum physics!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>Fine judge all you want but... married a lesbian, left a man at the altar, fell in love with a gay ice dancer, threw a girl&#x2019;s wooden leg in the fire, LIVE IN A BOX.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>siliconvalley</tvserie>
      <content>Jian-Yang, what're you doing? This is Palo Alto. People are lunatics about smoking here. We don't enjoy all the freedoms that you have in China.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>got</tvserie>
      <content>Do the dead frighten you?</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>drwho</tvserie>
      <content>Big flashy things have my name written all over them. Well... not yet, give me time and a crayon.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>twinpeaks</tvserie>
      <content>Cooper, you may be fearless in this world, but there are other worlds.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>got</tvserie>
      <content>Never forget who you are. The rest of the world won't. Wear it like an armor and it can never be used against you.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>simpsons</tvserie>
      <content>When will I learn? The answers to life&#x2019;s problems aren&#x2019;t at the bottom of a bottle, they&#x2019;re on TV!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>drwho</tvserie>
      <content>Do what I do. Hold tight and pretend it&#x2019;s a plan!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>If the homo sapiens were, in fact, HOMO sapiens&#x2026;is that why they&#x2019;re extinct?</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>simpsons</tvserie>
      <content>Marriage is like a coffin and each kid is another nail.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>Guys can fake it? Unbelievable! The one thing that&#x2019;s ours!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>simpsons</tvserie>
      <content>Books are useless! I only ever read one book, To Kill A Mockingbird, and it gave me absolutely no insight on how to kill mockingbirds!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>drwho</tvserie>
      <content>This is my timey-wimey detector. It goes 'ding' when there's stuff.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>got</tvserie>
      <content>When you play a game of thrones you win or you die.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>got</tvserie>
      <content>Summer will end soon enough, and childhood as well.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>drwho</tvserie>
      <content>See the bowtie? I wear it and I don't care. That's why it's cool.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>siliconvalley</tvserie>
      <content>I firmly believe we can only achieve greatness if first, we achieve goodness</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>got</tvserie>
      <content>And so he spoke, and so he spoke, that Lord of Castamere, but now the rains weep o'er his hall, with no one there to hear. Yes, now the rains weep o'er his hall, and not a soul to hear.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>twinpeaks</tvserie>
      <content>Damn fine coffee! And hot!</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>drwho</tvserie>
      <content>If we're gonna die, let's die looking like a Peruvian folk band.</content>
    </quote>
    <quote>
      <tvserie>friends</tvserie>
      <content>Well, maybe he was nervous.</content>
    </quote>
  </quotes>
</root>
